William Bernardes Magalhães

Full-Stack Developer

william.b.magalhaes@gmail.com



wbmagalhaes.github.io

a github.com/wbmagalhaes

Profile

Self-taught programmer with experience in a variety of languages including C#, Python, and JavaScript. As a freelancer, I have worked on both front-end and back-end development and comfortable with agile development methodologies, having implemented websites, app features and mobile applications.

Able to effectively self-manage during independent projects, as well as collaborate as part of a productive team, I am excited to bring my skills and experience to a new challenge and I am confident in my ability to contribute to the success of a project.

Relevant Experience

Full-Stack Developer at SpaceWizard

August 2020 - Present

Development of applications and games written in C# in the Unity3D framework. Development of websites using HTML, CSS, JavaScript and React. Maintenance and configuration of git platform and repositories. Modeling and support of SQL and NoSQL databases.

Master in Chemistry at UEL

January 2018 - December 2020

Built and trained a convolutional neural network model with the Python framework TensorFlow, to classify images of coffee beans.

Our dataset was composed by 5000 images of raw Arabica coffee beans, classified as perfect and 9 types of common defects found in coffees sold in the Brazilian internal market. After training, the neural network had a ~80% accuracy on the testing data.

Bachelor in Chemistry at UEL

January 2014 - December 2014

Developed an Arduino colorimeter using LED and photodiode with an op-amp in transimpedance mode. All the instrument parts were developed by myself, including the circuitry and the user interface in C#.

Skills

Python

JavaScript

TypeScript

React

jQuery

HTML

CSS

SOL

Education

Doctor in Chemistry, UEL

Jan 2021 - Present

Master in Chemistry, UEL

Jan 2018 - Dec 2020

Bachelor in Chemistry, UEL

Jan 2011 - Dec 2016

Languages

Portuguese, English.

Hobbies

Games, roleplaying games, reading, traveling.